Margaret Henderson Floyd Architectural Slide Collection MS175
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Architectural slides, 1955 -- 1998; 1960 -- 1990; MS175.001; 16.0 Linear Feet
  - English geography, 1960 -- 1997; MS175.001.014
    - Alnwick Castle, 1970; MS175.001.027.00003 (Box 27)
    - Antony House, 1970; MS175.001.027.00004 (Box 27)
    - Athelhampton, 1971; MS175.001.027.00005 (Box 27)
    - Audley End, 1977; MS175.001.027.00006 (Box 27)
    - Bamberg Castle, 1970; MS175.001.027.00007 (Box 27)
    - Beaminster, 1971; MS175.001.027.00008 (Box 27)
    - Bedford Park, 1969; MS175.001.027.00009 (Box 27)
    - Beeston Castle, 1969; MS175.001.027.00010 (Box 27)
    - Bishop Aukland Castle, 1970; MS175.001.027.00011 (Box 27)
    - Blackheath, 1969; MS175.001.027.00012 (Box 27)
    - Blair Castle, 1971; MS175.001.027.00013 (Box 27)
    - Blake Hall, 1969; MS175.001.027.00014 (Box 27)
    - Bordsworth, 1970; MS175.001.027.00015 (Box 27)
    - Brownsea Island, 1971; MS175.001.027.00016 (Box 27)
    - Buxton, 1969; MS175.001.027.00017 (Box 27)
    - Callaly Castle, 1970; MS175.001.027.00018 (Box 27)
    - Cerne Abbas, 1971; MS175.001.027.00019 (Box 27)
    - Cheshire, 1969; MS175.001.027.00020 (Box 27)
    - Chatsworth, 1969; MS175.001.027.00021 (Box 27)
    - Chester 1, 1969; MS175.001.027.00022 (Box 27)
    - Chester 2, 1969; MS175.001.027.00023 (Box 27)
    - Chester 3, 1969; MS175.001.027.00024 (Box 27)
    - Chillingham Castle, 1970; MS175.001.027.00025 (Box 27)
    - Calstock, 1971; MS175.001.027.00026 (Box 27)
    - Compton Wynyates, 1969; MS175.001.027.00027 (Box 27)
    - Cotehele House, 1971; MS175.001.027.00028 (Box 27)
    - Cromford, 1969; MS175.001.027.00029 (Box 27)
    - Dorcester, 1971; MS175.001.027.00030 (Box 27)
    - Dorset / Canford Manor, 1971; MS175.001.027.00031 (Box 27)
    - Dulwich, 1969; MS175.001.027.00032 (Box 27)
    - Duncombe, 1970; MS175.001.027.00033 (Box 27)
    - Durham, 1969 -- 1970; MS175.001.027.00034 (Box 27)
    - Inventory, 1997; MS175.001.028.00001 (Box 28)
    - Eccleston House, 1969; MS175.001.028.00002 (Box 28)
    - Edensor, 1969; MS175.001.028.00003 (Box 28)
    - Encombe House, 1960 -- 1990; MS175.001.028.00004 (Box 28)
    - Eton College, 1969; MS175.001.028.00005 (Box 28)
    - Forde Abbey, 1969 -- 1971; MS175.001.028.00006 (Box 28)
    - Greenwich, 1969; MS175.001.028.00007 (Box 28)
    - Haddon Hall, 1969; MS175.001.028.00008 (Box 28)
    - Hampton Court, 1973; MS175.001.028.00009 (Box 28)
    - Ilkley, 1971; MS175.001.028.00010 (Box 28)
    - Isle of Portland, 1971; MS175.001.028.00011 (Box 28)
    - Jedburgh Abbey, 1971; MS175.001.028.00012 (Box 28)
    - Knutsford, 1969; MS175.001.028.00013 (Box 28)
    - Lanhydrock, 1971; MS175.001.028.00014 (Box 28)
    - Lincoln, 1969; MS175.001.028.00015 (Box 28)
    - Lindisfarne, 1970; MS175.001.028.00016 (Box 28)
    - Liverpool, 1970; MS175.001.028.00017 (Box 28)
    - London [1], 1969 -- 1971; MS175.001.028.00018 (Box 28)
    - London [2], 1969; MS175.001.028.00019 (Box 28)
    - London/Kensington [1], 1969 -- 1973; MS175.001.028.00020 (Box 28)
    - Kensington [2], 1973; MS175.001.028.00021 (Box 28)
    - Lumley Castle, 1970; MS175.001.028.00022 (Box 28)
    - Melbury, 1971; MS175.001.028.00023 (Box 28)
    - Melcombe Regis, 1971; MS175.001.028.00024 (Box 28)
    - Michelham, 1969; MS175.001.028.00025 (Box 28)
    - Milton Abbey, 1971; MS175.001.028.00026 (Box 28)
    - Minterne House, 1971; MS175.001.028.00027 (Box 28)
    - Montacute [1], 1971; MS175.001.028.00028 (Box 28)
    - Montacute [2], 1971; MS175.001.028.00029 (Box 28)
    - Morton, 1978; MS175.001.028.00030 (Box 28)
    - Newark, 1969; MS175.001.028.00031 (Box 28)
    - Osborne House, 1970; MS175.001.028.00032 (Box 28)
    - Plymouth [1], 1971; MS175.001.028.00033 (Box 28)
    - Plymouth [2], 1971; MS175.001.028.00034 (Box 28)
    - Powder House, 1971; MS175.001.028.00035 (Box 28)
    - Inventory, 1997; MS175.001.029.00001 (Box 29)
    - Rievaulx Abbey, 1970; MS175.001.029.00002 (Box 29)
    - [Roker], 1970; MS175.001.029.00003 (Box 29)
    - Ruthven, 1971; MS175.001.029.00004 (Box 29)
    - [Salisbury], 1971; MS175.001.029.00005 (Box 29)
    - Scarborough, 1970; MS175.001.029.00006 (Box 29)
    - [Sherbourne Abbey], 1971; MS175.001.029.00007 (Box 29)
    - Southwell Minster, 1969; MS175.001.029.00008 (Box 29)
    - Stover, 1971; MS175.001.029.00009 (Box 29)
    - Surrey, 1978; MS175.001.029.00010 (Box 29)
    - Sutton Scarsdale, 1969; MS175.001.029.00011 (Box 29)
    - Stonehenge, 1971; MS175.001.029.00012 (Box 29)
    - Stratford-Upon-Avon, 1971; MS175.001.029.00013 (Box 29)
    - Tatton Park, 1969; MS175.001.029.00014 (Box 29)
    - Weymouth, 1971; MS175.001.029.00015 (Box 29)
    - [Windsor], 1969; MS175.001.029.00017 (Box 29)
    - [Woodstock], 1971; MS175.001.029.00018 (Box 29)
    - Womersley, 1970; MS175.001.029.00019 (Box 29)
    - [Wykham], 1970; MS175.001.029.00020 (Box 29)
    - [York Minster], 1970; MS175.001.029.00021 (Box 29)
  - English architects, 1960 -- 1997; MS175.001.015
    - Inventory, 1997; MS175.001.030.00001 (Box 30)
    - R. Adam/ Saltram HSE, 1972; MS175.001.030.00002 (Box 30)
      Adam, Robert, 1728-1792
    - R. Adam#2/ Brizlee Tower, 1970 -- 1973; MS175.001.030.00003 (Box 30)
    - Ch. Barry/ Houses of Parliament, 1968 -- 1969; MS175.001.030.00004 (Box 30)
      Barry, Charles, 1823-1900
    - Ch. Barry/ Houses of Parliament, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.030.00005 (Box 30)
    - Ch. Barry #2/ Mt. Felix/ Traverlers and Reform Club, 1969 -- 1972; MS175.001.030.00006 (Box 30)
    - Barry&Banks/ Dulwich College New, 1969 -- 1973; MS175.001.030.00007 (Box 30)
      Barry, Charles, 1823-1900; Banks, Robert Richardson
    - Barry&Banks/ Dulwich New College, 1969; MS175.001.030.00008 (Box 30)
    - E.M. Barry/ Charring Cross Hotel-London, 1972; MS175.001.030.00009 (Box 30)
      Barry, Edward M. (Edward Middleton), 1830-1880
    - W. Beckford/ Baker Tower /Cuthbert Brodrick Grand Hotel, 1970 -- 1972; MS175.001.030.00010 (Box 30)
      Beckford, William; Brodrick, Cuthbert, 1821-1905
    - Berlage, 1969; MS175.001.030.00011 (Box 30)
    - Edward Blore, 1969; MS175.001.030.00012 (Box 30)
      Blore, Edward, 1787-1879
    - Bodley and Garner, 1969; MS175.001.030.00013 (Box 30)
      Bodley and Garner
    - Bastard Brothers, 1971; MS175.001.030.00014 (Box 30)
      Bastard, John, ca. 1688-ca. 1770; Bastard, William, ca. 1689-ca. 1766
    - James Brooks [and two illegible labels], 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.030.00015 (Box 30)
      Brooks, James, 1825-1901
    - I.K. Brunel, 1970 -- 1978; MS175.001.030.00016 (Box 30)
      Brunel, Isambard Kingdom, 1806-1859
    - WM. Burges/ Trinity College Hartford, CT, 1972 -- 1977; MS175.001.030.00017 (Box 30)
      Burges, William, 1827-1881
    - Lord Burlington, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.030.00018 (Box 30)
      Burlington, Richard Boyle, Earl of, 1694-1753
    - WM. Burn/ Harlaxton, 1969; MS175.001.030.00019 (Box 30)
      Burn, William, 1789-1870
    - Decimus Burton/ Palm Stove at Kew, 1969 -- 1973; MS175.001.030.00020 (Box 30)
      Burton, Decimus, 1800-1881
    - Butterfield/ All Saints Margaret St., 1969; MS175.001.030.00021 (Box 30)
      Butterfield, William, 1814-1900
    - Butterfield #2, 1969 -- 1971; MS175.001.030.00022 (Box 30)
    - [Colin Campbell], 1970; MS175.001.030.00023 (Box 30)
    - Sir William Chambers, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.030.00024 (Box 30)
      Chambers, William, Sir, 1723-1796
    - Champneys/ Newnham College, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.030.00025 (Box 30)
      Champneys, Basil, 1842-1935
    - Ewan Christian, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.030.00026 (Box 30)
      Christian, Ewan, 1814-1895
    - P. Clarke, 1969; MS175.001.030.00027 (Box 30)
      Clarke, Joseph, 1819-1881
    - C.R. Cockerell, 1969; MS175.001.030.00028 (Box 30)
      Cockerell, C.R. (Charles Robert), 1788-1863
    - J.K. Colling/ Albany Block Liverpool, 1970; MS175.001.030.00029 (Box 30)
      Colling, James Kellaway
    - J.K. Colling #2, 1970; MS175.001.030.00030 (Box 30)
    - J.K Coling #3/ Ashwicke Hall, 1972; MS175.001.030.00031 (Box 30)
    - J.K. Colling #4/Grammar of Ornament, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.030.00032 (Box 30)
    - Crossland/ Sanatorium Virginia Water, 1972 -- 1974; MS175.001.030.00033 (Box 30)
      Crossland, W.H. (William Henry), 1835-1908
    - Inventory, 1997; MS175.001.031.00001 (Box 31)
    - Deane/Woodward [1], 1970 -- 1978; MS175.001.031.00002 (Box 31)
      Deane, Thomas Newenham; Woodward, Benjamin
    - Deane/Woodward [2], 1970; MS175.001.031.00003 (Box 31)
    - Devey, George, 1977; MS175.001.031.00004 (Box 31)
      Devey, George
    - Dobson, John, 1970; MS175.001.031.00005 (Box 31)
      Dobson, John
    - Douglas, J, 1969; MS175.001.031.00006 (Box 31)
      Douglas, John
    - Eales, Christopher, 1971; MS175.001.031.00007 (Box 31)
      Eales, Christopher
    - Elmes/Cockerell, 1970; MS175.001.031.00008 (Box 31)
      Elmes, Harvey Lonsdale; Cockerell, Charles Robert
    - Fergusson, 1970; MS175.001.031.00009 (Box 31)
      Fergusson, James
    - Ferrey, Benjamin, 1971; MS175.001.031.00010 (Box 31)
      Ferrey, Benjamin
    - Foulston, 1971; MS175.001.031.00011 (Box 31)
      Foulston, John
    - George, Ernest/Peto, 1972 -- 1985; MS175.001.031.00012 (Box 31)
      George, Ernest; Peto, Harold A. (Harold Ainsworth)
    - Gibbard, Frederick, 1970; MS175.001.031.00013 (Box 31)
      Gibberd, Frederick
    - Gibbs, James, 1973; MS175.001.031.00014 (Box 31)
      Gibbs, James
    - Hardwick, Thomas, 1971; MS175.001.031.00015 (Box 31)
      Hardwick, Thomas
    - Harris, Martin/Harris, 1971; MS175.001.031.00016 (Box 31)
      Harris, Martin
    - Harrison, Thomas, 1969; MS175.001.031.00017 (Box 31)
      Harrison, Thomas
    - Hartley, James, 1970; MS175.001.031.00018 (Box 31)
      Hartley, Jesse
    - Hawksmoor, Nicholas, 1981; MS175.001.031.00019 (Box 31)
      Hawksmoor, Nicholas
    - Jones, Inigo, 1969 -- 1972; MS175.001.031.00020 (Box 31)
      Jones, Inigo
    - Jones, Owen [1], 1973; MS175.001.031.00021 (Box 31)
      Jones, Owen
    - Jones, Owen [2], 1960 -- 1990; MS175.001.031.00022 (Box 31)
    - Jones, Owen [3], 1971; MS175.001.031.00023 (Box 31)
    - Kerr, Robert, 1969 -- 1971; MS175.001.031.00024 (Box 31)
      Kerr, Robert
    - Lutyens [1], 1970; MS175.001.031.00025 (Box 31)
      Lutyens, Edwin Landseer, Sir
    - Lutyens [2], 1960 -- 1990; MS175.001.031.00026 (Box 31)
    - Malton, J/An Essay on British Architecture, 1960 -- 1990; MS175.001.031.00027 (Box 31)
      Malton, James
    - Medwin, R. Gardner-, 1970; MS175.001.031.00028 (Box 31)
      Medwin, R. Gardner-
    - Morris, William [1], 1977; MS175.001.031.00029 (Box 31)
      Morris, William
    - Morris, William [2], 1960 -- 1990; MS175.001.031.00030 (Box 31)
    - Nesfield, W.E., 1969 -- 1972; MS175.001.031.00031 (Box 31)
      Nesfield, William Eden
    - Newman, Robert, 1971; MS175.001.031.00032 (Box 31)
      Newman, Robert
    - Paine, James, 1969; MS175.001.031.00033 (Box 31)
      Paine, James
    - Paley/Austin, 1960 -- 1990; MS175.001.031.00034 (Box 31)
      Austin, Hubert J.; Paley, Edward Graham
    - Pearson, J.L., 1960 -- 1990; MS175.001.031.00035 (Box 31)
      Pearson, J. L. (John Loughborough)
    - Pitt, John, 1971; MS175.001.031.00036 (Box 31)
      Pitt, John
    - Inventory, 1997; MS175.001.032.00001 (Box 32)
    - Prestwich, Ernest, 1971; MS175.001.032.00002 (Box 32)
      Prestwick, Ernest
    - Pritchard, T.F., 1970; MS175.001.032.00003 (Box 32)
      Pritchard, Thomas Farnolls
    - Pugin, A.W.N. [1], 1972; MS175.001.032.00004 (Box 32)
      Pugin, Augustus Welby Northmore, 1812-1852
    - Pugin, A.W.N. [2], 1960 -- 1990; MS175.001.032.00005 (Box 32)
    - Pugin, A.W.N. [3], 1960 -- 1990; MS175.001.032.00006 (Box 32)
    - Pugin, A.W.N. [4], 1969; MS175.001.032.00007 (Box 32)
    - Pugin, A.W.N. [5], 1969; MS175.001.032.00008 (Box 32)
    - Pugin, A.W.N. [6], 1960 -- 1990; MS175.001.032.00009 (Box 32)
    - Pugin, A.W.N. [7], 1960 -- 1990; MS175.001.032.00010 (Box 32)
    - Pugin, Edward W., 1970; MS175.001.032.00011 (Box 32)
      Pugin, Edward Welby, 1834-1875
    - Rennie, John, 1971; MS175.001.032.00012 (Box 32)
      Rennie, John, Sir, 1794-1874
    - Rickman, Thomas, 1969; MS175.001.032.00013 (Box 32)
      Rickman, Thomas, 1776-1841
    - Ruskin, John/Stones of Venice Volume I, 1976 -- 1978; MS175.001.032.00014 (Box 32)
      Ruskin, John, 1819-1900
    - Ruskin, John/Stones of Venice Volume II, 1976; MS175.001.032.00015 (Box 32)
    - Ruskin, John/Stones of Venice Volume III, 1976 -- 1977; MS175.001.032.00016 (Box 32)
    - Ruskin, John/Seven Lamps of Architecture, 1971; MS175.001.032.00017 (Box 32)
    - Salvin, Anthony/Mamhead House [1], 1972; MS175.001.032.00018 (Box 32)
      Salvin, Anthony, 1799-1881
    - Salvin, Anthony/Mamhead House [2], 1971 -- 1972; MS175.001.032.00019 (Box 32)
    - Salvin, Anthony/Peckforton Castle/St. Paul's Alnwick/Thoresby Hall, 1969 -- 1970; MS175.001.032.00020 (Box 32)
    - Scott, Baillie, 1960 -- 1990; MS175.001.032.00021 (Box 32)
      Scott, Mackay Hugh Baillie, 1865-1945
    - Scott, Gilbert G. [1], 1969 -- 1977; MS175.001.032.00022 (Box 32)
      Scott, George Gilbert, Sir, 1811-1878
    - Scott, Gilbert G. [2], 1969 -- 1977; MS175.001.032.00023 (Box 32)
    - Seddon, J.P., 1970; MS175.001.032.00024 (Box 32)
      Seddon, John Pollard, 1827-1906
    - Sertes, Michael, 1969; MS175.001.032.00025 (Box 32)
      Sertes, Michael
    - Shaw, Norman [1], 1971; MS175.001.032.00026 (Box 32)
      Shaw, Richard Norman, 1831-1912
    - Shaw, Norman [2], 1970; MS175.001.032.00027 (Box 32)
    - Shaw, Norman [3], 1970; MS175.001.032.00028 (Box 32)
    - Shaw, Norman [4], MS175.001.032.00029 (Box 32)
    - Shaw, Norman [5], 1969 -- 1971; MS175.001.032.00030 (Box 32)
    - Inventory, MS175.001.033.00001 (Box 33)
    - Smythson #1 / Bolsover / Wollaton, 1969; MS175.001.033.00002 (Box 33)
      Smythson, Robert
    - Smythson #2 / Hardwick Hall, 1969; MS175.001.033.00003 (Box 33)
    - Smythson #3 / Burton Agnes Hall, 1970; MS175.001.033.00004 (Box 33)
    - Sir John Soane, 1981; MS175.001.033.00005 (Box 33)
      Soane, John, Sir
    - J. J. Stephenson, 1971; MS175.001.033.00006 (Box 33)
      Stephenson, J. J.
    - G. E. Street / Howsham Church / St. James the Less / Densten Church / St. James Kingsten, 1971; MS175.001.033.00007 (Box 33)
      Street, George Edmund (1824-1881)
    - G. E. Street / Constantinople Memorial Church / St. Phillip + St. James / Law Carts, 1971; MS175.001.033.00008 (Box 33)
    - Bruce Talbert / Barfield of Leicester, 1972; MS175.001.033.00009 (Box 33)
      Talbert, Bruce
    - Tecton, 1969; MS175.001.033.00010 (Box 33)
      Tecton
    - W. Aubrey Thomas, 1970; MS175.001.033.00011 (Box 33)
      Thomas, W. Aubrey
    - Francis Thompson, 1969; MS175.001.033.00012 (Box 33)
      Thompson, Francis
    - William Tite, 1969; MS175.001.033.00013 (Box 33)
      Tite, William
    - Van Brugh / Blenheim / Van Brugh's Castle, 1969 -- 1971; MS175.001.033.00014 (Box 33)
      Van Brugh, J.
    - Voysey / Mothecombe, 1969 -- 1972; MS175.001.033.00016 (Box 33)
      Voysey
    - [Voysey], 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.033.00017 (Box 33)
    - Voysey 1896 / J. Sturgis House, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.033.00018 (Box 33)
    - Voysey 1896 / J. Sturgis House, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.033.00019 (Box 33)
    - Lewis Vulliany, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.033.00020 (Box 33)
      Vulliany, Lewis
    - A. Waterhouse / Liverpool University / Waterhous Blg. Oxford / Museum of Natural History - London, 1969 -- 1970; MS175.001.033.00021 (Box 33)
      Waterhouse, A.
    - A. Waterhouse #2 / Museum of Natural History - London, 1968 -- 1969; MS175.001.033.00022 (Box 33)
    - A. Waterhouse Prudential Assurance London #3, 1981; MS175.001.033.00023 (Box 33)
    - R. H. Watts, 1969; MS175.001.033.00024 (Box 33)
      Watts, R. H.
    - [John Webb], 1969; MS175.001.033.00025 (Box 33)
      Webb, John
    - William White, 1971; MS175.001.033.00026 (Box 33)
      White, William
    - John Wood, 1970; MS175.001.033.00027 (Box 33)
      Wood, John
    - C. Wren #1, 1969 -- 1973; MS175.001.033.00028 (Box 33)
      Wren, Christopher, Sir
    - C. Wren #2, 1969; MS175.001.033.00029 (Box 33)
    - J. Wyatt, 1969 -- 1972; MS175.001.033.00030 (Box 33)
      Wyatt, James
    - T. H. Wyatt / St. Mary- St. Nicholas, 1969 -- 1972; MS175.001.033.00031 (Box 33)
      Wyatt, Thomas, Sir
    - Wyattville / Endsleigh, 1971; MS175.001.033.00032 (Box 33)
      Wyatville, Sir Jeffry (1766-1840)
  - German geography, 1990 -- 1996; MS175.001.016
    - Inventory, 1996; MS175.001.034.00001 (Box 34)
    - Travel itinerary, Germany, 1990; MS175.001.034.00002 (Box 34)
    - Berlin, Germany/ Berlin Cathedral [Berliner Dom], 1990; MS175.001.034.00003 (Box 34)
    - Berlin, Germany / Hackeschen Höfen / Handwerkervereinshaus, 1990; MS175.001.034.00004 (Box 34)
    - Berlin, Germany / Handwerkervereinshaus, 1996; MS175.001.034.00005 (Box 34)
    - Berlin, Germany/ Sophienstrasse, 1996; MS175.001.034.00006 (Box 34)
    - Dresden, Germany/ Japanese Palace [Japanischer Palais] / Martin Luther Statue/ Academy of Fine Arts [Hochschule für bildende Künste], 1990; MS175.001.034.00007 (Box 34)
    - Frankfurt, Germany / Hauptbahnhof, 1990; MS175.001.034.00008 (Box 34)
    - Jena, Germany / Zeiss Museum, 1990; MS175.001.034.00009 (Box 34)
    - Meissen, Germany / Building with Richardson eyelid window, 1990; MS175.001.034.00010 (Box 34)
    - Herringhausen, Germany / Romanesque church (12th century), 1990; MS175.001.034.00011 (Box 34)
    - Munich, Germany / Technical University [Technische Universität], 1990; MS175.001.034.00012 (Box 34)
    - Nuremberg, Germany / Unidentified slides [1], 1990; MS175.001.034.00013 (Box 34)
    - Nuremberg, Germany / Unidentified slides [2], 1990; MS175.001.034.00014 (Box 34)
  - German architects, 1990 -- 1997; MS175.001.017
    - Inventory, 1996; MS175.001.035.00001 (Box 35)
    - Martin Gropius / Museum of Dec. Arts / Art Museum and School [Martin-Gropius-Bau], 1990; MS175.001.035.00002 (Box 35)
      Gropius, Martin Philipp, 1824-1880
    - [Martin-Gropius-Bau] / North elevation, 1996; MS175.001.035.00003 (Box 35)
    - Martin-Gropius-Bau, Berlin, 1990; MS175.001.035.00004 (Box 35)
    - [Martin-Gropius-Bau], 1996; MS175.001.035.00005 (Box 35)
    - [Martin-Gropius-Bau], 1996; MS175.001.035.00006 (Box 35)
    - [Martin-Gropius-Bau], 1996; MS175.001.035.00007 (Box 35)
    - [Martin-Gropius-Bau] / North elevation, 1996; MS175.001.035.00008 (Box 35)
    - [Martin-Gropius-Bau] / North elevation, 1996; MS175.001.035.00009 (Box 35)
    - [Martin-Gropius-Bau] / West elevation, 1996; MS175.001.035.00010 (Box 35)
    - [Martin-Gropius-Bau] / West elevation, 1996; MS175.001.035.00011 (Box 35)
    - [Martin-Gropius-Bau] / West elevation, 1996; MS175.001.035.00012 (Box 35)
    - [Martin-Gropius-Bau] / West elevation, 1996; MS175.001.035.00013 (Box 35)
    - [Martin-Gropius-Bau] / West elevation (?), 1996; MS175.001.035.00014 (Box 35)
    - [Martin-Gropius-Bau] / East elevation, 1996; MS175.001.035.00015 (Box 35)
    - [Martin-Gropius-Bau] / East elevation, 1996; MS175.001.035.00016 (Box 35)
    - [Martin-Gropius-Bau] / East or West elevation (?), 1996; MS175.001.035.00017 (Box 35)
    - [Martin-Gropius-Bau], 1996; MS175.001.035.00018 (Box 35)
    - [Martin-Gropius-Bau], 1996; MS175.001.035.00019 (Box 35)
    - [Martin-Gropius-Bau], 1996; MS175.001.035.00020 (Box 35)
    - [Martin-Gropius-Bau], 1996; MS175.001.035.00021 (Box 35)
    - [Martin-Gropius-Bau], 1996; MS175.001.035.00022 (Box 35)
    - [Martin-Gropius-Bau], 1996; MS175.001.035.00023 (Box 35)
    - [Martin-Gropius-Bau], 1996; MS175.001.035.00024 (Box 35)
    - [Martin-Gropius-Bau], 1996; MS175.001.035.00025 (Box 35)
    - [Martin-Gropius-Bau], 1996; MS175.001.035.00026 (Box 35)
    - Heinrich Hübsch / Trinkhalle, Baden-Baden, 1990; MS175.001.035.00027 (Box 35)
      H&#00FC;bsch, Heinrich, 1795-1863
    - Heinrich Hübsch / Trinkhalle, Baden-Baden, 1990; MS175.001.035.00028 (Box 35)
    - Carl Ferdinand Langhans / [Staatsoper, Berlin], 1990; MS175.001.035.00029 (Box 35)
      Langhans, Carl Ferdinand, 1781-1869
    - Constantin Lipsius / Art Academy, Dresden / [Dresden Academy of Fine Arts, Hochschule für bildende Künste Dresden], 1990; MS175.001.035.00030 (Box 35)
      Lipsius, Constantin, 1832-1894
    - Adolf Loos [?] / Hackeschen Höfe, 1990; MS175.001.035.00031 (Box 35)
    - Julius Ludwig Rothweil / Arolsen Castle [Residenzschloss Arolsen], 1990; MS175.001.035.00032 (Box 35)
      Rothweil, Julius Ludwig, 1676 or 7-1750
    - Karl Friedrich Schinkel / Theater, Aachen / Berlin, 1990; MS175.001.035.00033 (Box 35)
      Schinkel, Karl Friedrich, 1781-1841
    - Schinkel / Bauakademie, 1997; MS175.001.035.00034 (Box 35)
    - Schinkel / Bauakademie, 1997; MS175.001.035.00035 (Box 35)
    - Schinkel / Bauakademie, 1997; MS175.001.035.00036 (Box 35)
    - Schinkel / Bauakademie, 1997; MS175.001.035.00037 (Box 35)
    - Gottfried Semper / Dresden / Statue of Gottfried Semper / Karibische Hütte / Cholerabrunnen, 1990; MS175.001.035.00038 (Box 35)
      Semper, Gottfried, 1803-1879
    - Gottfried Semper / Dresden / [Semperoper], 1990; MS175.001.035.00039 (Box 35)
    - Friedrich August Stüler / Berlin / Alte National Galerie, 1990; MS175.001.035.00040 (Box 35)
      St&#00FC;ler, Friedrich August, 1800-1865
    - Paul Troost / Modern Art Gallery / Haus der Kunst, Munich, 1990; MS175.001.035.00041 (Box 35)
      Troost, Paul Ludwig, 1879-1934
    - Friedrich von Gärtner / University, Munich / [Hauptgebäude der Ludwig-Maximillians-Universität], 1990; MS175.001.035.00042 (Box 35)
      G&#00E4;rtner, Friedrich von, 1792-1847
    - Leo von Klenze / Munich / Glyptothek, 1990; MS175.001.035.00043 (Box 35)
      Klenze, Leo, Ritter von, 1784-1864
    - Leo von Klenze / Munich / Propylaeum [Propylaea] / Alte Pinakothek, 1990; MS175.001.035.00044 (Box 35)
    - Leo von Klenze / Regensburg / Walhalla / Befreiungshalle, Rhine, 1990; MS175.001.035.00045 (Box 35)
    - Johannes Schilling / Dresden / Statue of Semper, 1990; MS175.001.035.00046 (Box 35)
      Schilling, Johannes, 1828-1910
    - Gabriel von Seidl / Bavarian National Gallery, Munich / [Bayerisches Nationalmuseum, 1990; MS175.001.035.00047 (Box 35)
      Seidl, Gabriel von, 1848-1913
    - Hermann Friedrich Waesemann / Berlin / Rotes Rathaus, 1990; MS175.001.035.00048 (Box 35)
      Waesemann, Hermann Friedrich, 1813-1879
    - Hermann Friedrich Waesemann / Berlin / Rotes Rathaus, 1990; MS175.001.035.00049 (Box 35)
    - Otto Wagner / Villa, Munich, 1990; MS175.001.035.00050 (Box 35)
      Wagner, Otto, 1841-1918
    - Georg Friedrich Ziebland / Königsplatz - Munich / [Staatliche Antikensammlungen], 1990; MS175.001.035.00051 (Box 35)
      Ziebland, Georg Friedrich
  - Central American, South American, US, and Spanish architecture, 1955 -- 1997; MS175.001.018
    - Travel Records, 1993; MS175.001.036.00001 (Box 36)
    - Guatamala and El Salvador, 1978 -- 1997; MS175.001.036.00002 (Box 36)
    - Cholula, Mexico / Santa Maria Tonantzintla / San Francisco Acatepec, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.036.00003 (Box 36)
    - Cholula, Mexico, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.036.00004 (Box 36)
    - Cholula, Mexico, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.036.00005 (Box 36)
    - Cholula, Mexico, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.036.00006 (Box 36)
    - Cholula, Mexico / Mexico 16th Century., 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.036.00007 (Box 36)
    - Cholula, Mexico / Interiors, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.036.00008 (Box 36)
    - Cholula, Mexico / Interiors, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.036.00009 (Box 36)
    - Guadalajara Vicinity, Mexico, 1978; MS175.001.036.00010 (Box 36)
    - Huejotzingo, Mexico, MS175.001.036.00011 (Box 36)
      Date Unknown.
    - Juarez, Mexico, 1955; MS175.001.036.00012 (Box 36)
    - Mexico City / Cathedral, 1970 -- 1997; MS175.001.036.00013 (Box 36)